Sa.
Hey, Emily. How's it going? Hey, fan.
How are you doing? All good. I'm all good. I'm super busy. I. I imagine you are the same. Yeah.
But, yeah, I mean, thank you for. For taking the time. I was looking at your calendar. I was. Okay.
I think that this is the. The perfect slot to put the 15 minute. Minute. And.
Yeah, so as the title says, I had like, a couple of days ago, I had a conversation with Paul.
So we.
So we want to start working on setting up a date for our next summit so we can start planning
it ahead of time. And the other thing is that we want to organize two summits this year.
One would be like a team summit probably for engineering team and the global summit that would take place around
Q4.
So this team summit we are thinking on organizing it by end of Q2 after kicking out fundraising, you know
like Paul has on his calendar that we will kick off and wrap up fundraising by Q2.
So that's what we are thinking about right now.
And yeah, so basically one of the main things he asked me to do is, I mean I'm going to
propose a couple of solutions.
Not solutions but options that we can work with in terms of days and potential locations.
But I want to work with the exec team and that's what I'm setting on these calls to get a
sense of their availability throughout those quarters ahead of time so we can know which days we can propose in
case you have any plans or something Locked already.
So yeah, basically that's the high level overview of the purpose of this call.
Okay, yeah, I'm pulling here, Give me one second. I created a spreadsheet with dates.
I'm sharing it with you via some chat.
So you can check the dates and you can mark like similar as we do as we did last time.
You can mark whether if you have like you are not available during any of these dates.
All right, let's see.
Something that Andrew suggested was planning the team summit around mid end of June.
So it could overlap with cycle planning. That could be interesting.
The company wide summit.
No, no, the team part like the one for June.
I see it.
Thanksgiving to start on Thursday. Right. I have market on Friday.
Yeah, it's on Thursday.
Yeah, I have it as notes like USA Thanksgiving just to take it into account. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, I mean I think in terms of like stuff I know I have. That's it.
Yeah, I, off the top of my head, I, I think that's all I got. Got it.
So I, I would say that for Q2 you are available, right?
Yeah.
Cool. Okay. I think that's, that's great. If, if something else comes up, let me know.
Well, you have the link to the spreadsheet so you can update it and yeah, if you have any ideas,
thoughts or suggestions around either the team summit or the global summit, let me know.
Well, I, I already gather everyone's feedback but especially for the bot summit.
Well, we are thinking engineering because it's the biggest team we have internally and yeah, I mean I think we
haven't done anything like in the last years with them and we are,
it would be for each pod.
So it'd be like engineering would have one design would have one like sales, customer service or.
I mean I don't, I don't think we're gonna do that.
We're gonna be able to do that like for all the parts this year.
Like, I don't think that's the goal.
I think it's just to do like a bigger, like kind of a mid level summit for a pod.
And yeah, I mean I have to still think about that more in detail with wall, but I think that
it makes sense right now to do it with engineering because they also are like including like the forecast is
that we're going to include and continue growing that team a lot.
So I think that it will be valuable for them to have like a in person week.
Okay.
Yeah. And potentially we're going to include the sign team in this summit as well. I think that makes sense.
Yeah. Product summit.
So I think that could make sense and given its product, overlapping it with planning could be great in terms
of roadmap. So. Yeah, I mean those are the high level thoughts right now I have gathered.
But yeah, I don't think we are going to be able to do like one for each spot this year.
Yeah, that's fine.
I was more so curious because I don't think I would go on the like product summit per se.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, I'm taking everyone into account just to get a sense of availability and we'll see which makes more sense.
Sounds good.
Okay, thank you. Ethan, let me know if you have any other thoughts. But yeah, that's it.
See Emily, thank you.